so let's look at the solution for our
latency inut quiz we have a website that
has two servers a server takes a
millisecond to process an order so the
latency of an
order is clearly 1 millisecond that's
how long it takes from the time the
order arrives until the time it is
actually served the throughput of a
single server because it cannot do
anything else while processing the order
is going to be
one order per millisecond or a th orders
per second but we have two such servers
so we can process 2,000 orders per
second so this illustrates again the
situation where the throughput is not
just equal to one over the latency if it
were like that we would have only 1,000
orders per second but we can buy more
throughput simply through replication of
servers in this case and thus achieve a
higher throughput
then the latency of a single server
would indicate